Guide to the Washington State University Irrigated Agriculture Research and Extension Center Photographs 1919-1969
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 1: Images created by WSU-Prosser staff, 1919-1969
  - Subseries 1: Dated images, 1919-1969
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.090)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.091)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.092)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.093)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.094)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.095)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.096)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.097)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.098)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.099)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.100)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.101)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.102)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.103)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.104)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.105)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP072. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.106)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.107)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.108)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.109)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.110)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.111)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.112)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.113)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.114)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.115)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.116)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.117)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.118)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.119)
    - Beef cattle. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.120)
    - Cattle on feed. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926-03-11 (Box 1, Item 26.121)
    - Cattle on feed. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926-03-11 (Box 1, Item 26.122)
    - Cattle on feed. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP073. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.123)
    - Cattle on feed. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.124)
    - Cattle on feed. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926-03-11 (Box 1, Item 26.125)
    - Cattle on feed. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926-03-11 (Box 1, Item 26.126)
    - Cattle on feed. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926-03-11 (Box 1, Item 26.127)
    - Cattle on feed. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926-03-11 (Box 1, Item 26.128)
    - Beef cattle in feed lots. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.129)
    - Steers on feed. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1926 (Box 1, Item 26.131)
    - Stacking Hay. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP074. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.001)
    - Cattle on Pasture. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.002)
    - Wheat Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.003)
    - Wheat Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.004)
    - Wheat Plots. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.005)
    - Wheat Plots. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.006)
    - Wheat Plots. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.007)
    - Wheat Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.008)
    - Wheat Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.009)
    - Wheat Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.010)
    - Dewits - Granger. Loading Wheat Bundles on Sled. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP352. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.011)
    - Stacking Wheat. Dewits, Granger. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP075. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.012)
    - Stacking Wheat. Dewits, Granger. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.013)
    - Stacking Wheat. Dewits, Granger. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP076. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.014)
    - Sodium Nitrate Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.015)
    - Nitrogen fertilizer plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.016)
    - Plot 1. Nitrogen Fertilizer Plots - Wheat. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.017)
    - Plot 1. Nitrogen Fertilizer Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.018)
    - Plot 1. Nitrogen Fertilizer Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.019)
    - Plot 1. Nitrogen Fertilizer Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.020)
    - Plot 2. Nitrogen Fertilizer Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.021)
    - Plot 2. Nitrogen Fertilizer Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.022)
    - Plot 4. Nitrogen Fertilizer Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.023)
    - Plot 3. Nitrogen Fertilizer Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.024)
    - Plot 5. Nitrogen Fertilizer Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.025)
    - Plot 5. Nitrogen Fertilizer Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.026)
    - Plot 6. Nitrogen Fertilizer Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.027)
    - Plot 9. Nitrogen Fertilizer Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.028)
    - Plot 10. Nitrogen Fertilizer Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.029)
    - Plot 12. Nitrogen Fertilizer Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.030)
    - Straw Plot - nitrogen Fertilizer Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.031)
    - Break in Sunnyside Canal. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.032)
    - Break in Sunnyside Canal. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.033)
    - Break in Sunnyside Canal. 3.5x5.5 neg.; print. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.034)
    - Break in Sunnyside Canal. 3.5x5.5 neg.; print. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.035)
    - Railroad culvert near Whitstran washed off by water from break in Sunnyside Canal. 3.5x5.5 neg.; print. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.036)
    - Road South of Station flooded by water from break in Sunnyside Canal. 3.5x5.5 neg.; print. WSUP077. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.037)
    - Orchard south of station flooded by water from break in Sunnyside Canal. 3.5x5.5 neg.; print. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.038)
    - Break in Sunnyside Canal. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.039)
    - Break in Sunnyside Canal. 3.5x5.5 neg.; print. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.040)
    - Break in Sunnyside Canal. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1 print, not of negative. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.041)
    - No Title. Person standing in field. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.042)
    - Weighing hay in field. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP078. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.044)
    - Hay weighing equipment. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.045)
    - Hay weighing equipment. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.046)
    - Holstein bull - Cascade Carrion. 1927 (Box 1, Item 27.047)
    - Dairy cattle on pasture. 1928 (Box 1, Item 28.001)
    - Wheat Field. 1928 (Box 1, Item 28.002)
    - Thrashing Wheat. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP079. 1928 (Box 1, Item 28.003)
    - Thrashing Wheat. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP080. 1928 (Box 1, Item 28.004)
    - Thrashing Wheat. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP081. 1928 (Box 1, Item 28.005)
    - Thrashing Wheat. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1928 (Box 1, Item 28.006)
    - Thrashing plots in field. WSUP082. 1928 (Box 1, Item 28.007)
    - Thrashing plots in field. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP083. 1928 (Box 1, Item 28.008)
    - Rolling to compact seed bed. 2.5x4.25 neg. WSUP084. 1928 (Box 1, Item 28.009)
    - Lambs on feed. 1928 (Box 1, Item 28.010)
    - Binding Wheat. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP085. 1929 (Box 1, Item 29.001)
    - Sheep on sweet clover pasture. 1929 (Box 1, Item 29.002)
    - Wheat Plots. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1929 (Box 1, Item 29.003)
    - Bull Owned by Dairy Department - State College. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1930 (Box 1, Item 30.001)
    - Herd sire. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1930 (Box 1, Item 30.002)
    - Donald. Peach trees killed by application of potassium fertilizer in plowed furrows near trees. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1931 (Box 1, Item 31.001)
    - Donald. Peach trees killed by application of potassium fertilizer in plowed furrows near trees. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1931 (Box 1, Item 31.002)
    - Donald. Peach trees killed by application of potassium fertilizer in plowed furrows near trees. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1931 (Box 1, Item 31.003)
    - Fritz. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1931 (Box 1, Item 31.004)
    - Fritz. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1931 (Box 1, Item 31.005)
    - Lettuce seed crop. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1932 (Box 1, Item 32.001)
    - Lettuce seed crop. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1932 (Box 1, Item 32.002)
    - Lettuce seed crop. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1932 (Box 1, Item 32.003)
    - Lettuce seed crop. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1932 (Box 1, Item 32.004)
    - Lettuce seed crop. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1932 (Box 1, Item 32.005)
    - Lettuce seed crop. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1932 (Box 1, Item 32.006)
    - Lettuce seed crop. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1932 (Box 1, Item 32.007)
    - Lettuce seed crop. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1932 (Box 1, Item 32.008)
    - Lettuce seed crop. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1932 (Box 1, Item 32.009)
    - Lettuce seed crop. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1932 (Box 1, Item 32.010)
    - Lettuce seed crop. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1932 (Box 1, Item 32.011)
    - Lettuce seed crop. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1932 (Box 1, Item 32.012)
    - Hauling lettuce seed from field. 2.25x3.25 neg. WSUP086. 1932 (Box 1, Item 32.013)
    - Apple orchard. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1932 (Box 1, Item 32.014)
    - Apple Orchard. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1932 (Box 1, Item 32.015)
    - Skinner Place. Cooperative fertilizer plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1932 (Box 1, Item 32.016)
    - Cooperative fertilizer plots in Skinner place. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1932 (Box 1, Item 32.017)
    - Skinner Place. Cooperative fertilizer plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1932 (Box 1, Item 32.018)
    - Cooperative fertilizer plots in Skinner place. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1932 (Box 1, Item 32.019)
    - Skinner Place. Cooperative fertilizer plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1932 (Box 1, Item 32.020)
    - Skinner Place. Cooperative fertilizer plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1932 (Box 1, Item 32.021)
    - Yakima River at flood stage. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1933-12-23 (Box 1, Item 33.001)
    - Yakima River at flood stage. 2.5x4.25 neg. WSUP087. 1933-12-23 (Box 1, Item 33.002)
    - Yakima River at flood stage. Joyland Park near Mabton. 2.5x4.25 neg.; print. 1933-12-23 (Box 1, Item 33.003)
    - Yakima River at Flood Stage. 2.5x4.25 neg.; print. 1933-12-23 (Box 1, Item 33.004)
    - Yakima River at Flood Stage. 2.5x4.25 neg.; print. 1933-12-23 (Box 1, Item 33.005)
    - Yakima River at F;lood Stage. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1933-12-23 (Box 1, Item 33.006)
    - Yakima River at Flood Stage. 2.5x4.25 neg.; print. 1933-12-23 (Box 1, Item 33.007)
    - Yakima River at Flood Stage from Granger Bridge. 2.5x4.25 neg.; print. 1933-12-23 (Box 1, Item 33.008)
    - Yakima River at flood Stage. 2.5x4.25 neg.; print. 1933-12-23 (Box 1, Item 33.009)
    - Yakima River Flood Stage. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1933-12-23 (Box 1, Item 33.010)
    - Yakima River at Flood Stage. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1933-12-23 (Box 1, Item 33.011)
    - Yakima River at Flood Stage. 2.5x4.25 neg. WSUP088. 1933-12-23 (Box 1, Item 33.012)
    - Yakima River at Flood Stage. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1933-12-23 (Box 1, Item 33.013)
    - Yakima River at Flood Stage. 2.5x4.25 neg. WSUP089. 1933-12-23 (Box 1, Item 33.014)
    - Yakima River at Flood Stage. Prosser bridge?. 2.5x4.25 neg. WSUP090. 1933-12-23 (Box 1, Item 33.016)
    - Yakima River at Flood Stage. Prosser Dam?. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1933-12-23 (Box 1, Item 33.017)
    - Yakima River at Flood Stage. Not Prosser Bridge?. 2.5x4.25 neg.; print. 1933-12-23 (Box 1, Item 33.018)
    - Yakima River at Flood Stage. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1933-12-23 (Box 1, Item 33.019)
    - Yakima River at Flood Stage. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1933-12-23 (Box 1, Item 33.020)
    - Yakima River at Flood Stage. 2.5x4.25 neg.; print. 1933-12-23 (Box 1, Item 33.021)
    - Yakima River at Flood Stage. 2.5x4.25 neg.; print. 1933-12-23 (Box 1, Item 33.022)
    - Yakima River. Orchard below Wapato Diversion Dam. 2.5x4.25 neg.; print. 1933-12-23 (Box 1, Item 33.023)
    - Yakima River at Flood Stage. 2.5x4.25 neg.; print. 1933-12-23 (Box 1, Item 33.024)
    - Radraw Thrasher. 2.5x4.25 neg. WSUP091. 1933 (Box 1, Item 33.027)
    - Radraw Thrasher. Similar to 33.27. 2.5x4.25 neg. WSUP092. 1933 (Box 1, Item 33.028)
    - Detail of Cylinder and Concave Rodrow Thrasher. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1933 (Box 1, Item 33.029)
    - Alfalfa Fertilizer Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1933 (Box 1, Item 33.030)
    - Thrashing with Small Machine. 2.5x4.25 neg. WSUP093. 1933 (Box 1, Item 33.032)
    - Wire Tree Bracing. 2.25x3.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.001)
    - Wire Tree Bracing. 2.25x3.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.002)
    - Yellow Madrid Sweet Clover. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.003)
    - Yellow Madrid Sweet Clover. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.004)
    - Red Field Yellow Sweet Clover. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.005)
    - Red Field Yellow Sweet Clover. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.006)
    - Red Field Yellow Sweet Clover. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.007)
    - Red Field Yellow Sweet Clover. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.008)
    - Stone's Early Sweet Clover. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.009)
    - Stone's Early Sweet Clover. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.010)
    - Stone's Early Sweet Clover. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.011)
    - Alfalfa / Sweet clover. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.012)
    - Alfalfa / Sweet clover. 2.5x3.25 neg. No prints. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.013)
    - Alfalfa / Sweet clover. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.014)
    - Alfalfa / Sweet clover grown as cover crop in orchard. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.015)
    - Alfalfa / Sweet Clover Grown in Nursery Row. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.016)
    - Alfalfa and White Madrid Grown in Nursery Row. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.017)
    - Alfalfa / Sweet Clover Grown in Nursery Row. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.018)
    - Alfalfa / Sweet Clover Grown in Nursery Row. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.019)
    - Alfalfa and Sweet Clover. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.020)
    - Grundy County White Sweet Clover. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.021)
    - Grundy County White Sweet Clover. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.022)
    - Grundy County White Sweet Clover. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.023)
    - Grundy County White Sweet Clover. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.024)
    - Grundy County White Sweet Clover. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.025)
    - White Madrid sweet clover. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.026)
    - White Madrid sweet clover grown in nursery row. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.027)
    - White Madrid sweet clover. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.028)
    - White Madrid sweet clover. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.029)
    - White Madrid sweet clover. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.030)
    - Lespedeza servicia. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.031)
    - Side delivery rake. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP329. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.032)
    - Weighing Hay Samples in Field. 3.5x5.5 neg. WSUP094. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.034)
    - Dairy Calves. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.035)
    - Calf. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.036)
    - Calf. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.037)
    - Calf. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.038)
    - Calf. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.039)
    - Calf. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.040)
    - Young tree after pruning. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.041)
    - Alfalfa Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.043)
    - Alfalfa Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.044)
    - Harvesting Sweet Clover Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.045)
    - Harvesting Sweet Clover Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. WSUP095. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.046)
    - Harvesting Sweet Clover Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.047)
    - Harvesting Sweet Clover Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.048)
    - Harvesting Sweet Clover Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. WSUP096. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.049)
    - Harvesting Sweet Clover Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.050)
    - Harvesting Sweet Clover Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.051)
    - Harvesting Sweet Clover Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. WSUP097. 1934 (Box 1, Item 34.052)
    - Field day. 2.5x4.25 neg. WSUP098. 1935-06-12 (Box 1, Item 35.002)
    - Sweet Clover Seed Crop. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1935 (Box 1, Item 35.005)
    - Alfalfa Plots. 3.5x5.5 neg. 1935 (Box 1, Item 35.006)
    - Sweet Clover Cover Crop in Pear Orchard. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1935 (Box 1, Item 35.007)
    - Alfalfa Plots. 2.5x4.25 neg. WSUP099. 1935 (Box 1, Item 35.008)
    - 2nd year Yellow Madrid just coming into blossom. N of Plot 11. Two photos on one 3.5x5.5 negative. 1936-05-22 (Box 2, Item 36.001a)
    - Orchard in Okanogan Valley. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1936 (Box 2, Item 36.001b)
    - 2nd year Yellow Madrid just coming into blossom. S of Plot 10. 5x7 neg. 1936-05-22 (Box 2, Item 36.002a)
    - Orchard in Okanogan Valley. 2.5x4.25 neg. WSUP100. 1936 (Box 2, Item 36.002b)
    - 2nd year volunteer sweet clover. Jenkins wheat in plots 13, 14. S of Plot 6; N of Plot 13. Two photos on one 5x7 negative. 1936-05-22 (Box 2, Item 36.003a)
    - Orchard in Okanogan Valley. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1936 (Box 2, Item 36.003b)
    - Okanogan Trip. Landscape. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1936 (Box 2, Item 36.004)
    - Okanogan Trip. Landscape. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1936 (Box 2, Item 36.005)
    - Okanogan Trip. 2.5x4.25 neg. 1936 (Box 2, Item 36.006a)
    - Planting potatoes on Field A 4. 5x7 neg. WSUP101. 1936-06-05 (Box 2, Item 36.006b)
    - Plot 1 alfalfa varieties 'Idaho Common'. SW of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-06-11 (Box 2, Item 36.007)
    - Plot 2 alfalfa varieties 'Arizona Common'. SW of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-06-11 (Box 2, Item 36.008)
    - Plot 4 alfalfa varieties 'South Dakota #121'. SW of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-06-11 (Box 2, Item 36.009)
    - Plot 9, 'Hardistan'. SW of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-06-11 (Box 2, Item 36.010)
    - Plot 10, Variety tests, 'Hardigan'. SW of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-06-11 (Box 2, Item 36.011)
    - Plot 12, 'Ladak'. SW of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-06-11 (Box 2, Item 36.012)
    - Plot 13, 'Idaho Grimm'. SW of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-06-11 (Box 2, Item 36.013)
    - Plot 14, 'North Dakota Grimm'. SW of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-06-11 (Box 2, Item 36.014)
    - Second yr. Alpha 1 sweet clover crop. N. end of 2 A Norton pear orchard. 5x7 neg. 1936-06-11 (Box 2, Item 36.015)
    - Second year Alpha 1 sweet clover crop. N. end of 2 A Norton pear orchard. 5x7 neg. 1936-06-11 (Box 2, Item 36.016)
    - Arizona Common. E edge of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-06-11 (Box 2, Item 36.017)
    - Henry Holtz Fert. Plot. This plot receives an annual application of straw. Plot 1. N of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-18 (Box 2, Item 36.018)
    - Henry Holtz Fert. Plots. This plot receives an annual application of sodium nitrate. Plot 2. N of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-18 (Box 2, Item 36.019)
    - Plot 3 of Henry Holtz Fert. Plots. Check plot. N of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-18 (Box 2, Item 36.020)
    - Plot 4 of Henry Holtz Fert. Plots. This plot receives an annual application of ammonium sulphate. N of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-18 (Box 2, Item 36.021)
    - Plot 5 of Henry Holtz Fert. Plots. This plot receives an annual application of fish scraps. N of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-18 (Box 2, Item 36.022)
    - Plot 6 of Henry Holtz Fert. Plots. This plot receives an annual application of yard manure. N of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-18 (Box 2, Item 36.023)
    - Plot 13 Henry Holtz Fert. Plots. Check plot. N of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-18 (Box 2, Item 36.024)
    - Plot 14 of Henry Holtz Fert. Plots. Annual application of N, P and K. N of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-18 (Box 2, Item 36.025)
    - Plot 15 of Henry Holtz Fert. Plots. This receives an annual application of N and P. N of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-18 (Box 2, Item 36.026)
    - Plot 16 of Henry Holtz Fert. Plots. Annual application of N and K. N of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-18 (Box 2, Item 36.027)
    - Plot 7 of Henry Holtz Fert. Plots. Annual application of sodium nitrate and gypsum. N of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-18 (Box 2, Item 36.028)
    - Plot 17 of Henry Holtz Fert. Plots. Annual application of N and K. N of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-18 (Box 2, Item 36.029)
    - Plot 18 of Henry Holtz Fert. Plots. Check plot. N of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-18 (Box 2, Item 36.030)
    - No Description, no date, subject. 3.5x2.5 neg.; print. 1936-07-18 (Box 2, Item 36.030a)
    - Plot 19 of Henry Holtz Fert. Plots. Annual application of N, P and K. N of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-18 (Box 2, Item 36.031)
    - Plot 19 of Henry Holtz Fert. Plots. Annual application of N, P and K. N of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-18 (Box 2, Item 36.032)
    - Cereal Plots. W end of cereal variety plots. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-17 (Box 2, Item 36.034)
    - Plot 7 of Henry Holtz Fert. Plots. Gypsum and sodium nitrate. N of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-17 (Box 2, Item 36.035)
    - Plot 8 of Henry Holtz Fert. Plots. Check plot. N of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-17 (Box 2, Item 36.036)
    - Plot 10 of Henry Holtz Fert. Plots. Annual application of sheep manure. N of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-17 (Box 2, Item 36.037)
    - Plot 11 of Henry Holtz Fert. Plots. Annual application of treble superphosphate. N of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-17 (Box 2, Item 36.038)
    - Plot 12 of Henry Holtz Fert. Plots. Annual application of potassium sulphate. N of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-17 (Box 2, Item 36.039)
    - Plot 9 of Henry Holtz Fert. Plots. Annual application of alfalfa hay. N of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-17 (Box 2, Item 36.040)
    - Crop rotation plots. S end of the wheat series. 5x7 neg. 1938-07-16 (Box 2, Item 36.043)
    - North Dakota Grimm. SW of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-27 (Box 2, Item 36.044)
    - Ladak alfalfa, second cutting. SW of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-27 (Box 2, Item 36.045)
    - Arizona Common, 2nd cutting. SW of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-27 (Box 2, Item 36.046)
    - Hemet, Calif. Common, second cutting. SW of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-27 (Box 2, Item 36.047)
    - Turkestan alfalfa, second cutting. Height shown by plane in front of board. Hay badly down. SW of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-27 (Box 2, Item 36.048)
    - Hardigan alfalfa, second cutting. SW of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-27 (Box 2, Item 36.049)
    - Hardistan, 2nd cutting. Hay down badly. SW of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-27 (Box 2, Item 36.050)
    - Modoc Calif. Common. SW of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-27 (Box 2, Item 36.051)
    - South Dakota #12, second cutting. SW of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-27 (Box 2, Item 36.052)
    - South Dakota #12, second cutting. SW of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-27 (Box 2, Item 36.053)
    - Second cutting Arizona Common. SW of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-27 (Box 2, Item 36.054)
    - Second cutting Idaho Common.Second cutting Arizona Common. Hay down some on this plot. SW of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-27 (Box 2, Item 36.055)
    - Dusting tomatoes. On left, dusted with sulphur and rotanane on right. Fiedl H. W. Henkey, Pasco. S of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-29 (Box 2, Item 36.056)
    - Arizona Common (second cutting). 5x7 neg. 1936-07-27 (Box 2, Item 36.057)
    - Arizona Common 2nd cutting. 5x7 neg.; print. 1936-07-27 (Box 2, Item 36.058)
    - So. Dak. #12, second cutting. End of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-27 (Box 2, Item 36.059)
    - Alfalfa plots. Ariz. Common in foreground. End of plots. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-28 (Box 2, Item 36.060)
    - Alfalfa plots. Arizona Common in foreground. East of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-28 (Box 2, Item 36.061)
    - Alfalfa plots. Arizona Common in foreground. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-28 (Box 2, Item 36.062)
    - Arizona Common. East of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1936-07-27 (Box 2, Item 36.063)
    - Hemet, Calif. Common. East of plot. 5x7 neg. 1936-07-27 (Box 2, Item 36.064)
    - Strawberry clover. 5x7 neg. 1936-08-17 (Box 2, Item 36.065)
    - Virgin soil vs. orchard soil for starting cover crops. Dull orchard. Wenatchee. 5x7 neg. 1936-08-14 (Box 2, Item 36.067)
    - Virgin soil vs. treated orchard soil for starting cover crops. West of plots. Dull orchard. Wenatchee. 5x7 neg. 1936-08-14 (Box 2, Item 36.068)
    - Raking 10" Alfalfa for Poultry Work. Alfalfa. 5x7 neg. WSUP102. 1936-08-05 (Box 2, Item 36.069)
    - Cutting 10" hay for poultry work. South of plots. 5x7 neg. 1936-08-05 (Box 2, Item 36.070)
    - Young alfalfa 10", cut for poultry work. South of alfalfa plots. 5x7 neg. 1936-08-05 (Box 2, Item 36.071)
    - Native vegetation. Sagemoor fine sandy loam. North of P. J. Taggares road. 5x7 neg. 1936-08-18 (Box 2, Item 36.072)